Subtitle Provide by dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.asia [Admin.@YNG]
=Lust and Lies=
=الشهوة والكذب=
Here.
هنا.
=Episode 19=
=الحلقة 19=
Put me down!
ضعني في الأسفل!
Let go of me!
أتركني!
Why?
لماذا؟
Are you trying to hold me captive?
هل تحاول أن تأسرني؟
If you dare try anything funny again,
إذا تجرأت على تجربة أي شيء مضحك مرة أخرى،
I don't mind holding you captive here.
لا مانع لدي من احتجازك هنا.
It should be the other way around, no?
ينبغي أن يكون الأمر بالعكس، أليس كذلك؟
That way,
بهذه الطريقة،
at least you won't betray me.
على الأقل لن تخونني.
Is your engagement with Sheng Weilian
هل خطوبتك مع شينغ ويليان؟
considered a betrayal?
هل يعتبر خيانة؟
The Lion Seal?
أسد البحر؟
Didn't you warn me?
ألم تحذرني؟
A true revenge
انتقام حقيقي
is not without a plan.
ليس بدون خطة.
And we shouldn't act recklessly.
ولا ينبغي لنا أن نتصرف بتهور.
This shall be your bargaining chip.
هذه ستكون ورقة المساومة الخاصة بك.
And this is my reward for you.
وهذه هي مكافأتي لك.
♪In a gentle night♪
♪في ليلة لطيفة♪
♪A bare face awaiting blush♪
♪وجه عارٍ ينتظر الاحمرار♪
♪Cups clink, voices overlap♪
♪أكواب تتصادم، أصوات متداخلة♪
♪We switch our roles♪
♪نحن نبدل الأدوار♪
♪Darkness fades, and daylight breaks♪
♪يتلاشى الظلام، ويشرق ضوء النهار♪
♪Evening winds usher in the night♪
♪رياح المساء تبشر بقدوم الليل♪
♪All fading away♪
♪كل شيء يتلاشى♪
Where is Huo Xiu?
أين هو شيو؟
He's not back yet.
إنه لم يعود بعد
If he doesn't return with her body,
إذا لم يعود بجثتها،
you'll go
سوف تذهب
and get rid of them both.
وتخلص منهما كلاهما.
But
لكن
Governor,
محافظ،
the Huo family and the Sheng family
عائلة هوو وعائلة شنغ
have had a marriage alliance, no?
لقد كان لديك تحالف زواج، أليس كذلك؟
Mr. Sheng.
السيد شنغ.
You won't mind
لن تمانع
having a dead bride, do you?
هل لديك عروس ميتة؟
Not at all.
مُطْلَقاً.
Everyone in Sucheng
الجميع في سوتشنغ
is aware of our marriage alliance.
على علم بتحالف زواجنا.
Our families
عائلاتنا
are
نكون
on the same boat.
على نفس القارب.
It doesn't matter
لا يهم
if the bride is dead or alive.
إذا كانت العروسة حية أو ميتة.
You're right, Governor.
أنت على حق يا سيدي الحاكم.
I'm feeling kind of unwell.
أنا أشعر بنوع من التوعك.
I need to head back now.
أحتاج إلى العودة الآن.
Hold on.
يتمسك.
You should pay respect to my son first.
ينبغي عليك احترام ابني أولاً.
Do you still remember it?
هل لازلت تتذكره؟
Back then,
في ذلك الوقت،
you blindfolded me and told me
لقد عصبت عيني وأخبرتني
it's just a killing act.
إنها مجرد عملية قتل.
You're here to kill me, no?
أنت هنا لقتلي، أليس كذلك؟
I won't do that.
لن افعل ذلك
But if one of us
ولكن إذا كان أحدنا
must die today,
يجب أن يموت اليوم
you should do it.
ينبغي عليك أن تفعل ذلك.
You're not Huo Qingwan.
أنت لست هيو تشينغوان.
Am I right?
هل انا على حق؟
I'm the Huofeng Gang's mistress.
أنا عشيقة عصابة هووفينج.
My surname is Ruan.
لقبي هو روآن.
My name is Ruan Feifei.
اسمي روآن فايفي.
I can now
انا استطيع الان
tell you who I am.
أخبرك من أنا.
This is the Lion Seal?
هذا هو أسد البحر؟
It's just an ordinary pebble.
إنها مجرد حصاة عادية.
And this is the Lion Seal.
وهذا هو أسد البحر.
The former governor of Sucheng
الحاكم السابق لسوتشينج
died fifteen years ago.
توفي منذ خمسة عشر عامًا.
I've heard of him.
لقد سمعت عنه.
He collaborated with the Japanese
لقد تعاون مع اليابانيين
and sold our country out.
وبِيعنا بلادنا.
Here's the treaty signed with the Japanese under the table.
وهنا المعاهدة التي تم توقيعها مع اليابانيين تحت الطاولة.
It's all about interests
كل شيء يتعلق بالاهتمامات
and treasonous terms.
وشروط خيانية.
Huo Beishan?
هوو بيشان؟
Huo Beishan
هوو بيشان
was a mere dock worker.
كان مجرد عامل رصيف.
He gained Gu Changqing's favour
لقد حصل على تأييد غو تشانغتشينغ
and joined the the Gu Army.
وانضم إلى جيش جو.
Who would've thought he'd laid the entire Gu to family waste?
من كان يظن أنه سيدمر كل أفراد العائلة؟
He even forcibly married Madam Gu.
حتى أنه تزوج السيدة جو قسرا.
Madam.
سيدتي.
Don't be afraid.
لا تخف.
I won't hurt you.
لن أؤذيك.
You animal!
يا حيوان!
You planted all those crimes on the Gu family!
لقد زرعت كل هذه الجرائم على عائلة جو!
You even plotted to kill Changqing...
حتى أنك خططت لقتل تشانغتشينغ...
If I hadn't destroyed the Gu family,
لو لم أدمر عائلة جو،
how could I have become Sucheng's governor?
كيف أصبح حاكما لسوتشينج؟
Let me go!
دعني أذهب!
Let go!
اتركه!
Can you bring yourself
هل يمكنك إحضار نفسك؟
to kill Gu Changqing's child?
لقتل طفل جو تشانغتشينغ؟
You should stay alive
يجب عليك البقاء على قيد الحياة
and be my wife.
وتكون زوجتي.
Then you can get back at me.
وبعدها يمكنك الرد علي.
♪Feelings I can't shake off♪
♪مشاعر لا أستطيع التخلص منها♪
♪Quietly emerge♪
♪الظهور بهدوء♪
So
لذا
Madam Gu was your mother?
هل كانت السيدة قو أمك؟
You were Gu Changqing's son?
هل كنت ابن قو تشانغتشينغ؟
Now you know why
الآن تعرف السبب
Huo Beishan got upset
انزعج هوو بيشان
over your earrings.
فوق أقراطك.
Because that has to do with the Gu family's blood feud.
لأن ذلك له علاقة بالثأر الدموي لعائلة جو.
Huo Beishan
هوو بيشان
became reputable by eradicating traitors in Sucheng.
أصبح مشهورًا باستئصاله الخونة في سوتشنغ.
Who would have thought
من كان يظن
he's the ungrateful traitor here?
إنه الخائن الجاحد هنا؟
This Lion Seal
هذا الأسد الفقمة
can be used
يمكن استخدامها
to access an account at Henglong Bank.
للوصول إلى حساب في بنك Henglong.
♪Listen, the bell rings from afar♪
♪استمع، الجرس يرن من بعيد♪
♪The fog lifts, your image still hazy♪
♪يرتفع الضباب، وصورتك لا تزال ضبابية♪
♪Do you remember the sound of the flute in the wind?♪
♪هل تتذكر صوت الناي في الريح؟♪
♪It whispers of the flame we shared♪
♪همس من اللهب الذي شاركناه♪
♪Having seen those prophecies left behind♪
♪بعد أن رأيت تلك النبوءات التي تركوها وراءهم♪
♪A sudden will to survive arises♪
♪تنشأ فجأة رغبة في البقاء♪
♪The ruan resounds with grandeur♪
♪الروان يتردد صداه بالعظمة♪
♪Under the pelting plum rain♪
♪تحت المطر الغزير من البرقوق♪
♪Everyone sings the final act♪
♪الجميع يغني الفصل الأخير♪
♪All fading away♪
♪كل شيء يتلاشى♪
♪The curtain falls♪
♪الستار يسقط♪